Sulaiman Jalloh



Pro. Graphic Designer

(232) 72 889-690 (232) 30 889-690



sulaimancreation@gmail.com

13 Adolphus Street, Kissy, Freetown Sierra Leone, West Africa

I want to utilize my skills in problem solving. computer graphics application in as visual design concept.

Profile

With 3+ years experience and have an exceptional knowledge in developing graphics, audio and visual images for product illustrations, logos and Flyers.

I am passionate and enthusiastic to design and have the capability to create extraordinary designs with high visual impact according to the needs and requirements of the clients.

Besides, I have the awareness of the competitive business environment and can think creatively and have the capability to develop new designs, concepts and layouts that fit the clients' needs which will 7 out the competition.

I have exceptional knowledge of colors, images, text style, and layout and can develop designs for small businesses, large corportions and individuals.

Education

2014 - 2017

West African Senior School Certificate Examination (WASSCE)

2017 - 2019

Certificate in Computer Software and Graphic Design.

Personal Skills

Coursework

PHOTOSHOP ILLUSTRATOR



COREL DRAW INDESIGN



Work Experience

TEACHING 2019-2020

GRAPHIC DESIGN 2019-2020 I have been teaching at Kalibondo Computer School Software and Online as well.

I have been working as freelance Graphic Designer since I finish my course online.